{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "谁",
      "answer": "Shéi | who, whom"
    },
    {
      "question": "来",
      "answer": "Lái | to come"
    },
    {
      "question": "介绍",
      "answer": "Jièshào | to introduce"
    },
    {
      "question": "名字",
      "answer": "Míngzì | name"
    },
    {
      "question": "中文",
      "answer": "Zhōngwén | Chinese"
    },
    {
      "question": "爸爸",
      "answer": "Bàba | dad"
    },
    {
      "question": "学习",
      "answer": "Xuéxí | to study, to learn"
    },
    {
      "question": "学",
      "answer": "Xué | to study, to learn"
    },
    {
      "question": "专业",
      "answer": "Zhuānyè | major, speciality"
    },
    {
      "question": "美术",
      "answer": "Měishù | fine arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "美",
      "answer": "Měi | beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "文学",
      "answer": "Wénxué | literature"
    },
    {
      "question": "系",
      "answer": "Xì | faculty, department"
    },
    {
      "question": "加拿大",
      "answer": "Jiānádà | Canada"
    },
    {
      "question": "美国",
      "answer": "Měiguó | the United States of America"
    }
  ]
}
